(Yin Jisheng)
(Zheng Liyu)
"Thunderstorm"
So he came from your kindergarten, right?
Does he himself know about this?
know
Because he left the kindergarten when he was 6 years old
Already had a personal will at that time
A philanthropist who has long supported him
Will help children be adopted into families at home and abroad
The sponsor’s name is…
yes
i know who he is
he is my uncle
Why did my uncle adopt Yizhao...
It's relatively easy to adopt a child who doesn't realize he's been abandoned
But when you get to that age, you're usually very averse to adoption.
Li Yizhao was the oldest child in the orphanage at that time
It is presumed that the last remaining child
Adopted by the sponsor
But I heard that it’s because I don’t have the consent of my spouse.
So there is no way to officially adopt him.
Really
OK
thank you for your reply
Zhenghan, there are things I didn’t tell you
You should feel cheated by me
I know everything. Damn it, I know you slept with Xu Zhengyin.
I said I don't care anymore. Damn it, why are you still like this?
Li Yizhao, are you really...
Zhenghan, are you okay?
Yeah
It's a photo
you have a high fever
am i dreaming
It seems like it's true
Am I dying?
Get up first and drink porridge, then take medicine later
Is it a photo?
Are you really a photo?
Otherwise, are there any fake ones?
Will fall down
Why did you come just now?
I've been waiting for you
Let’s drink porridge first
evil
So unpalatable
Not...
No...I mean it tastes tasteless
Because I have a stuffy nose
Hurry up and finish eating. Go take medicine.
I'm leaving first
Remember to take medicine on time
Don't
I want to die directly from this illness
Could you please stop talking like this?
Let's see where you dare to go
Don't go
stay with me
What if I hurt you and it hurts more?
no one can hurt me
If Xu Zhengyin finds out...
don't worry
Xu Zhengyin was arrested and imprisoned
what
Because he takes drugs
Xu Zhenghan, are you really...
I will get rid of those who hurt you one by one
What else do you need me to help you get rid of?
You should lie down and rest first.
come here
It's about why you came back suddenly
Because of the relationship between repair and effectiveness
What Zhang Xiuxiao?
Yeah
Do you really not know about Yizhao being threatened?
Does it really have nothing to do with you?
Threat?
Not Zhenghan
Really
Xu Zhengyin’s foul mouth said this guy’s name
Let's go first, okay?
why do you say it
Didn't I tell you?
Zhenghan doesn’t know about this
How can you be sure that he doesn't know?
This timing is just perfect, right?
As soon as the news came out that there was going to be a city update near that house,
Xu Zhenghan is close to you
Xu Zhengyin will threaten you
i know
I know that matter has nothing to do with Zhenghan
Since you are so sure
Why do you still want to break up with Xu Zhenghan?
And why on earth are you insisting on not selling the house?
Because I'm a human again
Dad and Zhenghan are no longer with me.
If I gave up my house
I'm really alone
What about me?
Am I some kind of invisible person?
sorry
One photo
Yeah
You have always lived for others
It's time to live for yourself
Don't worry about others
according to your heart
do what you want
That's what Xu Zhenghan and I look forward to most
what do you want to do now
I want to stay with Junghan
go ahead
Go to that guy quickly
I want to stay by your side
Did anyone say no?
I said I would help you get rid of them
Your dad...
my uncle
Ah...I can't get rid of my dad
And we're not blood cousins either.
So what
How do you know about this...
How could you be so stupid
He is not your biological father
You took care of him for 9 years and wasted your youth.
Say sorry to Seo Jung-in who has nothing to do with you
Listen to those weird things he said about you being an illegitimate child
He also said you could understand him
You can still laugh
are you stupid
We just use different methods
ways to love each other
that moment
I was shocked
A photo in front of me
Originally it always looked so small
Very distressing
Very pitiful
But the person who became small is actually me
Zhengyin, that doesn’t work
I can understand Zhengyin
Wasn't his father suddenly taken away from him?
Of course he might hate me
Yi Zhao knows how to apologize
Also willing to be hated
I just want to...
Give him the love I got
Zhenghan
Love has no reason
No cost
At least my love is like that
He knows how to love
Also know how to be loved
always love openly
love sincerely
That's it
I dare not say easily that I know Yizhao very well
A photo in front of me
His mere presence makes people feel extremely oppressive
It’s pure, shiny, and beautiful
i love you
i love you too
That's right
Love may also be called awe
But
I don’t want to hear about you from other people in the future.
OK
I will tell you everything in the future
Let’s talk again
Is there anyone else I need to remove?
Ah…
your exes
I don't like murderers very much...
What would you do if I turned into a murderer?
Leave me behind and walk away alone?
Let's wander around the world for the rest of our lives
Alas
Don't look at me like that
why
Because I want to kiss you
Just kiss me
No
My cold will be passed on to you
I've never been infected with a cold in my life
Don't do this. It's really contagious.
You really don’t listen to me
Not listening so quickly
I said it's contagious
No
No... I just told you no
Hello
OK
-Yizhao -Yeah
Get up and drink the porridge before taking medicine.
Why is Porridge angry?
I told you clearly that it’s contagious. Please don’t kiss me.
Hello
How
I've never had a cold in my life
Hate…
Come and open your mouth
How is it
Delicious
Really?
Oh
Come
I will be the one to cook from now on
'Later'?
Yeah
One photo
Let’s not care about other people’s eyes from now on
If you want to do something, just do it.
Want to do something?
Well, whatever you want, I will do it for you
What's wrong
what is
Tell me about it
Will I buy you a house?
I'd rather buy you a car
I want to get my high school diploma
Still want to go to college
I want to find something I'm good at
Just do it all
If I'm going to do this I need time and money
Do you think I can’t even give you this investment?
I need a long, long time
i know
It takes four years to go to college
If I want to find out what I'm good at
may take longer
Does it have to go to this point?
i want to have
I…
I want to own your future
i know
-I'm a little greedy. -Here you go.
my future
Leave it to you
I knew it would be like this
That's why I didn't say it
How can you just exchange your future with me?
come here
One photo
I'm not a fuel-efficient lamp
It means I won’t give everything, only you are the only one
Anyway, what you mean is that you like me too much
You just let me go because you don't want to ruin my future.
I don't really like it that much...
Hello
The atmosphere is just right now. If you insist...
It hurts. I'm sick. Zhenghan
-Yeah, I know. -I feel bad.
lie down…
(2 months later)
Thanks
It seems your dad is very angry
Stop talking
It was not easy to save my life
look at this bruise
Can't you be smarter and date him secretly?
Why do you have to be so honest?
I want to be frank
face one's feelings
You are also a talent
In the end, I defeated your amazing father.
I am the only son in my family
Other relatives are as sick as Xu Zhengyin
Even my dad wouldn't be able to do it, right?
But I said I would be in charge of overseas branches
Hey, but you don’t care about the consequences no matter what you do.
You're like this and there's nothing anyone can do to you
It just made Yi Zhao Xin very tired.
Didn’t you say you haven’t seen each other for more than a month?
Are you my friend or Yizhao's friend?
Oh, you waste
Hey, I'm a patient
But what about a photo?
Won't he set off with you?
Well, we agreed to meet at the airport
I'm leaving thanks
Zhenghan
What are you doing?
Will he really come?
what
Take a photo
If…
He didn't show up there. What are you going to do?
I'm curious
Such Li Yizhao
Why do you want to leave me?
I have nothing
How come you have nothing?
You all have me
You have me who has everything
So you have everything
Is that so?
One photo
Yeah
I have something curious
I…
I really decided to leave my future to you.
I want to be your family
Even if there are occasional misunderstandings and quarrels
let each other get hurt
I also want to be that kind of person with you who won’t have conflicts because of these
and severed relationship
So you...
are you ready
(One photo, I’m leaving)
It's a photo
The sound of footsteps running towards me
Even if it's a faint sound coming from afar
Just a photo
I'll definitely recognize it
One photo, are you ready?
I'm ready
Where's uncle's house?
It doesn't matter
Now I have something I want to protect more.
Is there something you want to protect?
you and me
all belong to you
my future my present
And my past
And I
I caught the weight of the future that rushed into my arms with all its strength.
caught you
when will it arrive
It's hot, right?
Just another five minutes or so of walking…
You just said it was five minutes
How do you manage to live in a rural place like this?
Oh what are you doing?
It looks like it's going to rain
Will it rain suddenly?
This is how it is here
It rained suddenly and stopped suddenly
Hey, go there and run.
It would be better if you didn't go back to Seoul
Hey, don't say such scary things
Let's wait until the rain stops before leaving.
I want to play with you forever
or
I hope you can come over during your holidays
Li Yizhao
Wouldn't it be nice if you came over?
Why do you always ask me to come?
Come here yourself